Guide to the Maurice Shapiro Environmental Health Collection, 1919-2001 UA.90.F65
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research Files, 1919-2000; IV.
  - Environmental Hygiene, 1939-1971; 4.
    - 4213- Housing in Europe, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 4214- Housing in the USA, 1949-1960 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 4215- Heating, 1954-1960 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 4216- Buildings for the handicapped and/or aged, 1951-1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 4217- Better population forecasting for areas and communities, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - 4218- Slum clearance and urban redevelopment, 1949-1955 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 4218- Slum clearance and urban redevelopment, 1955-1962 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 4219- Zoning, 1941-1958 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 4220- Housing research, 1951-1958 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 4221- Estimating the inbreeding coefficient, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 4222- Population genetics, 1953-1958 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 4223- Housing in hot weather, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - 4224- Housing sanitation, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 4225- Housing design, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - 4301- Dust, 1953-1961 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 4302- Noise, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - 4304- Radiation, 1957-1969 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 4400- Environmental health, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 4401- Performance measurement project, 1953-1961 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 4402- Radiological health, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - 4403- California Conferences of Local Health Officers, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 4404- Pollution and poisoning, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 4900- Host biology, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 4900.1- Clinical molecular biology, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 4900.2- Mutation, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Housing Code draft, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Food Sanitation, 1934-1972; 5.
    - 3001- Milk pasteurization, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 3101- Ordinances and codes, 1938-1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 3102- Microbiological examination, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 3103- Quality, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 3104- Ratings of milk sheds, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 3105- Production, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - 3107- Bovine mastitis, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - 3108- Brucellosis, 1941-1948 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 3109- Diseases spread by milk, 1934-1950 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - 3110- Milk sanitation, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - 3111- Pasteurization, 1946-1955 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - 3112- Milk inspection, 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 3201- Nutrition, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - 3202- Shellfish, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - 3300- Food sanitation, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 3300.1- Artificial additives and biologic effects, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 3301- Ordinances and codes, 1936-1957 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - 3302- Microbiological examination, 1949-1963 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - 3303- Contamination, 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - 3304- Refrigeration, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - 3304.1- Dispensing freezers, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - 3305- Food handlers, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - 3306- Food standards, 1940-1962 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - 3307- Food poisoning, 1944-1959 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - 3308- Food utensil sanitation, dishwashing, detergents, 1944-1959 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - 3309- Restaurant sanitation, 1947-1954 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - 3310- Soda fountain and luncheonette equipment, 1942-1957 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - 3311- Drink vending machines, paper cups and containers, 1949-1958 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - 3312- Food hygiene, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - 3313- Poultry sanitation and inspection, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - 3314- Food handling and sanitation for commercial establishments, 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - 3315- Report on Germicides in Dishwashing, 1947-1953 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - 3316- Cyclamates, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - 3318- Disinfection, 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - 3319- Food sanitation programs, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - 3320- Equipment meeting National Sanitation Foundation standards, 1955-1962 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 3810- Malaria vectors, undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - General, 1947-1972; 6.
    - 8101- Educational material, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - 8102- Statistics, 1949-1958 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - 8103- Home accident prevention, 1951-1956 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - 8104- Occupational hazards and prevention, 1951-1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 8202- Manpower, 1950-1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 8203- Atomic warfare, 1952-1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - 8204- Biological warfare, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 8205- Disaster control, 1941-1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 8206- United States Civil Defense, 1952-1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - 8300- Diseases, 1956-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 8301- Influenza, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 8302- Poliomyelitis, 1950-1952 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - 8303- Cancer, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - 8304- Tuberculosis, 1953-1959 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - 8305- Rabies, 1947-1954 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - 8306- Industrial dermatitis, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 8307- Communicable diseases, 1946-1959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - 8308- Venereal disease, 1950-1958 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - 8309- Bacteria, viruses, parasites, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - 8310- Malaria, 1946-1959 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - 8311- Oral manifestations of occupational origin, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - 8312- Plague, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - 8314- RH, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - 8316- Brucellosis, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - 8317- Infectious hepatitis, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - 8318- Epidemic exanthema, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - 8319- Hookworm disease, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - 8320- Other diseases, 1951-1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - 8321- Beryllosis, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - 8322- Radiation-induced diseases, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - 8323- Schistosomiasis, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 8324- Heart disease, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - 8325- Foodborne and waterborne diseases, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - 8326- Yellow fever, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - 8328- Blood rheology, 1963-1969 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - 8328.1- Circulation, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - 8329- Heat stress, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - 8400- DDT, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - 8401- Chemical analysis, 1952-1959 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - 8401.1- Human storage, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - 8402- Ion exchange, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - 8403- Flotation, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - 8500- Industrial hygiene or occupational health, 1951-1956 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - 8500.1- Occupational health- Technical information services, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - 8501- Heat, 1952-1959 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - 8503- Human engineering, 1949-1956 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - 8504- Plant sanitation, 1949-1953 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - 8505- Clinical memoranda on economic poisons, 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - 8506- Operational memoranda on economic poisons, 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - 8509- Organizational health programs, 1960-1964 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - 8510- Air hygiene studies and industrial health, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - 8601- Publications, 1960-1971 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - 8601.1- Library, Graduate School of Public Health, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - 8601.2- Graduate School of Public Health job placement outline, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - 8603- Enzymology, 1954-1970 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - 8604- Weather, 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - 8606- Aerial photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - 8607- Appalachia, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - 8608- Bibliography, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - 8609- Morbidity and mortality, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - 8610- Civil engineering, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - 8611- Geology- Antarctica, undated (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - 8612- Census guides, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - 8613- Oceanic research, 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - 8614- Urban planning, 1960-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 8614.1- Transportation, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 8700- Equipment, 1950-1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 8700- Equipment, 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 8701- Instrumentation, water and sewage plants, 1956-1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 8702- Instrumentation, air pollution, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 8703.3- Radiation, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 8703.3- Radiation, 1959-1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 8703.4- Silt, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - 8703.6- Radioisotopes, 1960-1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - 8703.7- Atomic Energy Commission, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 8900- Economic growth, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - 8901- Mammalian scent marking, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - 8902- Costs versus benefits of increased electric power, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Key control to numbered files, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Air Pollution Control, 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Air Pollution Control Association, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Air Pollution Curriculum, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Air Pollution Practical Power Service Library, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Air Pollution Training Grant, 1955-1961 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - ALBRO Packing Company, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Allegheny County Boroughs Association, 1951-1955 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Allegheny County Health Department, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Allegheny College Health Association (ACHA)- Abstract Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Committee, Environmental Health, 1948-1962 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Informational Services, 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Liaison, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Newsletter, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Nominating, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Membership, 1957-1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Program, 1956-1962 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Program Papers, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Projects to be completed, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- Publications, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Allegheny College Health Association- 1961 materials (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - American Institute of Sanitary Engineers, 1953-1958 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - American Public Health Association, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1951-1954 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - American Sterilizer Company, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report: Air Sampling Results in Pittsburgh & Allegheny Power, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Associacion Interamericana de Ingenieria Sanitaria, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bedford Memorial Hospital, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Building Research Advisory Board, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Butler County, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - California Sewage Works Association, 1950-1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Citizen's Committee on Administration, Subcommittee on Personnel, 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Citizen's Committee on Environmental Health, Health and Welfare Federation of Allegheny County, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Citizen's Committee on Sanitation, 1953-1955 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Civil Defense, 1952-1955 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Civil Defense, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Community Chest Annual Report, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Copperweld Report to the State, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Dravo Corporation, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Engineering Science, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Federation of Sewage and Industrial Wastes Associations, 1951-1952 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Health and Welfare Federation of Allegheny County, 1955-1958 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Health and Welfare Federation of Allegheny County, 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Israeli Health Services, 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 20-21)
    - Johnstown Stream Survey, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Longvue Acres Sewage Treatment Plant, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Ludwig, Harvey F., 1951-1955 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - McCandless Township Sanitary Authority, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - McCandless Township Sanitary Authority, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - McCandless Township Sanitary Authority, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Pesticides, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Pesticides, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Pesticides, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Pesticides, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Public Health Services, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Public Health Services, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Public Health Services, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Soho and Lawrenceville, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - State Health Department- Alaska, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - State Health Department- California, 1951-1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - State Health Department- Georgia, 1947-1953 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - State Health Department- Illinois, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - State Health Department- Indiana, 1951-1953 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - State Health Department- Maryland, 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - State Health Department- New York, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - State Health Department- Ohio, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - State Health Department- Ohio, 1952-1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1950-1955 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1956-1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Water and Sewage Works Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1951 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Welch Grape Juice Company, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - West View Water Authority Softening Plant, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Wilkinsburg-Penn Joint Water Authority, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
  - Lead, 1958-1997; 7.
    - Allegheny County Health Department, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Analysis and measurements, 1971-1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - An Assessment of the Influence of Environmental Lead, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Baltimore, 1958-1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Boston, 1962-1976 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Burgess, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Burgess studies, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Soil Survey, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Chemistry, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Chicago, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Childhood Lead Poisoning, 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Childhood Lead Poisoning Control Programs, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - "Childhood Lead Poisoning by Ingestion", 1976 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Climatological information, 1969-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania contract, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - A Community Challenge: Management of Environmental Lead Hazards, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence- Commonwealth, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence- General, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - County lead, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Data file tables, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Department of Industrial Environmental Health Sciences, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Detroit, 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Distribution of Lead in the Air Near City Roads, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "Effect of Coal-Fired Electric Power Production on Mortality", 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Environmental lead, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Facts about Lead in the Air, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Final Report on Planning Grant to Evaluate Blood Lead Data for Children, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Focus on Childhood Lead Poisoning Prevention, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Fourth Annual Region V Childhood Lead Poisoning Prevention and Urban Rat Control Workshop, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - General, 1973-1980 (Box 22, Folder 17-24)
    - Grant planning, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Health Maintenance of Works Exposed to Inorganic Lead, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Housing in Allegheny County, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 27-28)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1976-1979 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Housing and Urban Development grant, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Identifying Sources of Lead Contamination by Stable Isotope Techniques, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The Influence of Air Lead Levels on the Body Burden of Lead and Blood Lead Levels of Children, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Journal articles, 1985-1989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Laboratory analysis, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
    - Lead-Based Paint Hazard Reduction Demonstration Project, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lead and health, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Lead poisoning, 1978-1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lead study, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Louisville, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Maps, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Memphis, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Metabolism, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Mining and Physiography, Allegheny County, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - National Academy of Science, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - New Haven/ Hartford, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper, 1959-1978 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Philadelphia, 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 23-24)
    - Phone contacts, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Policy and control, 1970-1979 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Projects, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Proposal, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Reports to Commonwealth, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Socio-economics, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Statistical Analysis of Blood Lead Levels of Children Surveyed in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Statistics, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Detroit: All Blood Lead Screening Records, File 1, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Detroit: Initial Blood Screening Records, File 2, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Detroit: Sequential Blood Lead Levels, File 3, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Detroit data printouts, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Detroit Lead Study Degression Runs, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Throop data- Computer printouts, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Throop data- Computer printouts, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2-4)
    - Throop, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - Public Health Administration, 1929-1971; 8.
    - 7100- Administration, general, 1945-1957 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - 7101- Industrial sanitation in state health departments, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 7102- Laws and codes, 1948-1962 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 7102.1- The Licensure System, 1959-1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 7103- Staffing standards for pay roll offices, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 7104- Time studies, 1945-1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 7105- Laboratory regulations, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - 7106- County health departments, 1950-1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - 7107- Guide to health organizations in the United States, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 7108- Health care objectives, 1929-1959 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 7109.1- American Public Health Association Epidemiology bibliography, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - 7110- Work standards, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - 7112- Planning for health services, 1958-1970 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - 7112.2- Health problems of elementary school children, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - 7112.2- Home care, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - 7113- Local health services, 1946-1962 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 7114- Local government, 1953-1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - 7114.1- Metropolitan planning, 1961-1970 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - 7115- Environmental Health Administration, 1952-1957 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - 7116- Research, 1955-1960 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - 7116.1- The Geochemical Environment, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - 7117- Salary information, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - 7118- Federal services, 1949-1963 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - 7120- Environmental quality, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - 7120- Environmental quality, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - 7120.1- Ekistics, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - 7120.3- Demography, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - 7121- Health and social problems, 1953-1970 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - 7200- Public health education, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - 7201- Evaluation schedule, 1944-1961 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - 7201.1- Environmental health programs, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - 7202- Environmental Health Center, 1953-1957 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - 7203- World health problems, 1951-1962 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - 7205.1- Health manpower, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - 7206- Occupational health, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - 7207- Basic drugs, 1956-1963 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - 7208- Jobs of councilmen, etc., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - 7209- Education in sanitary science, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - 7210- Related education, 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - 7210.1- Health education films, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - 7210.3- Smoking and health, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - 7210.4- Biophysical and biomedical education, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - 7210.5- Population, Statistical Report, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - 7210.6- HEW Research at SEC, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - 7210.7- Health Services Research and Development briefs, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - 7210.8- Nuclear explosives, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 7210.9- Publications report, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 7211- Schools of Public Health, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sanitation, 1947-1967; 9.
    - 6101- Camps and camping, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 6201- Hospital sanitation, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - 6202- School sanitation, 1952-1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - 6203- Home sanitation, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - 6204- Municipal sanitation, 1952-1958 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - 6205- Small commercial establishments, 1950-1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - 6301- Bacteriological study of automatic clothes washing, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - 6302- Insecticides, 1947-1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - 6302.1- Toxicological studies, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 6303- Pesticides, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - 6401- Rural sanitation, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - 6501- Railroad sanitation, 1951-1959 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 6502- Vessel and airlines sanitation, 1949-1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Sewage, 1933-1975; 10.
    - 2101- Individual sewage disposal systems, 1947-1954 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - 2101- Individual sewage disposal systems, 1956-1960 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - 2102- Septic tanks, 1949-1958 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - 2102- Septic tanks, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - 2200- Urban sewage, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - 2201- Laws, 1947-1957 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - 2202- Planning guide for commercial establishments and institutions, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - 2203- Standards, 1941-1960 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - 2204- Laboratory analysis, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - 2205- Copper sulphate for root and fungus control in sewers, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - 2206- Biochemical oxidation of sewage, 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - 2207- Thermasul- Sewage and water level control and indication, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 28)